BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail
  - Federal Labor Unions, Retail and Grocery, 1939-1940 (Box 132, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Retail Florists Employers Association of Seattle, Society of American Florists and Ornametal Horticulturalists, Washington Japanese Greenhouse Association and Florists Union, Federal Labor Union, Local 20975, AFL, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 2/7/1939 and expires on 2/7/1940. Covers 240 workers in Seattle, WA
    - Item 2: Albers Super Markets Inc. and Federal Labor Union, Local 20542, AFL, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 8/19/1939 and expires on 8/19/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 3: Pennsylvania Macaroni Company Incorporated and United Grocery Employees Union, Federal Labor Union, Local 20541, AFL, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 11/25/1939 and expires on 12/31/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in Pittsburgh, PA
  - Federal Labor Unions, Retail and Grocery, 1936-1942 (Box 132, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Minneapolis Petroleum Labor Committee and Gasoline Station Operators' Union, Local 19802, AFL, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1935 and expires on 9/30/1936. Covers an unknown number of workers in Minneapolis, MN
    - Item 2: Standard Oil Company, Shell Petro Company, Texaco Refq. Company, and others and Filling Station Attendants' and Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 19094, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1937 and expires on 4/1/1938. Covers 250 workers in East St. Louis, IL
    - Item 3: Filling Station Attendants' and Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 19565, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1937 and expires on 4/1/1938. Covers 125 workers in Alton, IL
    - Item 4: Gasoline Station Attendants Union of Greater New York, Local 20408, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 3/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 5: Cities Service Oil Company, Socony-Vacuum Company, Pocahontas Oil Corporation, and others and Gasoline Station Operators' Union, Local 18378, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 5/17/1937 and expires on 5/17/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 6: Filling Station Attendants' and Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 20437, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers.
    - Item 7: United Millinery Salesmen Union, Local 19866, AFL, 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 8/5/1937 and expires on 1/21/1939. Covers 300 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 8: Filling Station, Garage, and Parking Lot Employees' Union, Local 20664, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers 60 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 9: Retail Office Employers, Inc. and Office Employers Union, Local 16821, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1937 and expires on 11/1/1938. Covers 49 workers in Portland, OR
    - Item 10: United Gasoline Station Operators and Attendants Union and Local 20339, AFL, Gasoline Station Operators National Council, 1938-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1938 and expires on 12/31/1938. Covers 65 workers in Peru, IL
    - Item 11: Donaldson Motor Company and Retail Automobile Salemen's Union, Local 21991, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1941 and expires on 3/31/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Pittsburgh, PA
  - United Retail Employees, 1939-1945 (Box 132, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Shapleigh Hardware Company and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 543, CIO, 1939-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1939 and expires on 5/1/1941. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 2: Hamilton Supply Company and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 123, 1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1940. Covers 26 workers in Mather, PA
    - Item 3: Jas. H. Forbes Tea and Coffee Company and United Coffee, Tea and Spice Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 177A, CIO, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1940 and expires on 7/1/1941. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 4: Mahoning Supply Company and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 177, CIO, 1940-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 7/11/1940 and expires on 6/30/1942. Covers 21 workers in Yatesboro, PA
    - Item 5: Beef and Provision Company and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 487, CIO, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 8/5/1940 and expires on 8/5/1941. Covers 90 workers in Puxsutawney, PA
    - Item 6: Van Brode Milling Company, Inc. and United Wholesale and Warehouse Employees of New York, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 8/9/1940 and expires on 8/9/1941. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 7: Rockway Syrup Company, Haber Syrup Company, Mylo Syrup Company, and others and United Syrup and Preserves Employees Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 193, United Hebrew Trades, CIO, 1940-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1940 and expires on 4/1/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 8: Empire Ciy Syrup Manufacturers Association, Inc. and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 193, United Hebrew Trades, CIO, 1940-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 8/16/1940 and expires on 4/1/1943. Covers 150 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 9: Heinsheimer Brothers, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1940-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 10/8/1940 and expires on 11/24/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 10: Shapleigh Hardware Company, United Warehouse Employees, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 543, CIO, 1941-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1941 and expires on 4/30/1943. Covers 1569 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 11: Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 271, CIO, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1941 and expires on 5/1/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Kishi Valley, PA
    - Item 12: Butler Brothers and United Warehouse Employees, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 481, CIO, 1941-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/29/1941 and expires on 6/30/1943. Covers 237 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 13: Zadek Feldstein Company, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 9/27/1941 and expires on 9/27/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 14: Atlas China Company and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1941-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 10/17/1941 and expires on 10/16/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 15: Walter H. Johnson Candy Company and United Bakery and Confectionary Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 15, CIO, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1941 and expires on 11/1/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 16: Great Lakes Terminal Warehouse Company and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 363, CIO, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1941 and expires on 11/1/1942. Covers 60 workers in Toledo, OH
    - Item 17: Ideal Metal Products Company, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 1/20/1942 and expires on 1/15/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 18: Columbia Metal Frame Company and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 4/14/1942 and expires on 1/2/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 19: Libby, McNeill, and Libby and United Dairy Workers, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 88, CIO, 1942-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 4/24/1942 and expires on 4/1/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Grand Rapids, MI
    - Item 20: Frankfurth Hardware Company and United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, Local 174, CIO, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/20/1942 and expires on 3/16/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 21: Frank and Seder of Philadelphia, Inc. and United Retail and Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, Local 18, CIO, 1942-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/28/1942 and expires on 5/15/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 22: Lambert Novelty Mirror Works, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 8/13/1942 and expires on 8/13/1943. Covers 125 workers in Brooklyn, NY
    - Item 23: Sobel Brothers and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, Addendum, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 10/20/1942 and expires on 10/20/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 24: Metropolitan Displaymens Association, Inc. and Window Trimmers and Displayers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 144, CIO, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 11/9/1942 and expires on 7/31/1943. Covers 160 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 25: Samuel Berg Company and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1942-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 11/17/1942 and expires on 10/15/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 26: Leader Novelty Candy Company, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 11/24/1942 and expires on 10/14/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 27: Heinsheimer Brothers, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1942-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 11/25/1942 and expires on 11/25/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 28: Hyman and Hyman Beauty Products, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 12/1/1942 and expires on 11/11/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 29: Spicer Club and United Retail and Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, Local 64, Toledo Joint Board, CIO, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 12/26/1942 and expires on 12/26/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Toledo, OH
    - Item 30: Crisp Laundry Company and United Retail and Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, Local 92, CIO, 1943-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 2/26/1943 and expires on 1/20/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in Sault Ste. Marie, MI
    - Item 31: Bourjois, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1943-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1943 and expires on 5/1/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 32: United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, CIO, 1943-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/8/1943 and expires on 5/8/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in Savannah, GA
    - Item 33: Regal Shoe Company and United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, Local 327, CIO, 1943-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 5/18/1943 and expires on 10/18/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 34: Diamond Milk Products, Inc. and Dairy Workers Division, United Retail and Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, CIO, 1943-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1943 and expires on 9/30/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in Columbus, OH
    - Item 35: Save Electric Corporation and United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, Local 380, CIO, 1943-1945; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 12/1/1943 and expires on 4/24/1945. Covers 250 workers in Toledo, OH
    - Item 36: Association of Uptown Converters, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1944-1944; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 1/17/1944 and expires on 9/1/1944. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 37: Cardinal Parfums, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1944-1945; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 2/15/1944 and expires on 2/15/1945. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 38: Elray Kocke Service, Inc. and United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, CIO, 1944-1945; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 3/29/1944 and expires on 3/31/1945. Covers an unknown number of workers in Donaldsonville, LA
    - Item 39: Revlon Products Corporation and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 65, CIO, 1945-1945; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 1/10/1945 and expires on 12/31/1945. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
  - Retail Clerks Association, 1937-1940 (Box 132, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Port Angeles Merchant Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 375, 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 12/27/1937 and expires on 1/2/1939. Covers 90 workers in Port Angeles, WA
    - Item 2: Minneapolis Automobile Retail Salesmen's Association and Automobile Salesmen's Union, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1420, AFL, 1938-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 11/19/1938 and expires on 11/18/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in Minneapolis, MN
    - Item 3: King Arthur Food Markets and Grocery and Food Clerks' Union, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1245, AFL, 1938-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 11/22/1938 and expires on 11/22/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in Jersey City, NJ
    - Item 4: D. A. Schulte, Inc. and Retail Cigar Salesmen's Union, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 874, AFL, 1938-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 12/1/1938 and expires on 11/30/1940. Covers 150 workers in Boston, MA
    - Item 5: Kitsap County Food Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 381, AFL, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1939 and expires on 11/1/1940. Covers 203 workers in Bremerton, WA
    - Item 6: Association of Motor Vehicle Salesmen, Hudson and Terraplane Sales Corporation and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1415, AFL, Addendum, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 132, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 11/10/1939 and expires on 11/10/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
- Series X: Industry Code #45, Retail
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Tobacco shops and department stores
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Retail Department Store Employees, AFL, 1937-1939 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1937-1939 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1936-1939 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1936-1938 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1936-1937 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    formerly b74f3; formerly confidential
  - Retail Clerks, AFL, 1936-1939 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    Formerly b74f4
  - Wholesale and Retail Employees, CIO, 1939 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    retail cigar employees; formerly b74f7
  - Retail and Wholesale Employees, CIO, 1937-1940 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    Department store employees; formerly b74f10
  - Retail and Wholesale Employees, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    Formerly b74f12
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Retail Department Stores and Non-store Retailers, 1937-1939 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1940, Department Stores, Non-store Retail, Florists (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1942, Florists, 1929-1939 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1941, Department Store Retail, 1939-1941 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Series XI: Industry Code #48, Transportation
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (transportation), 1924-1938 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Longshoremen, general and California, 1920-1937 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Longshoremen, DE, FL, and IL, 1929-1939 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Longshoremen, LA and ME, 1921-1936 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Longshoremen, MD, 1929-1937 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Longshoremen, MI, MN, and MS, 1905-1936 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Longshoremen, NY, 1925-1936 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Longshoremen, OH, OR, and PA, 1929-1937 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Longshoremen, VA, 1929-1937 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Longshoremen, WA and Canada, 1921-1935 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Longshoremen and Waterfront Employers' Association, 1934-1937 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Longshoremen, MA, 1913-1937 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Longshoremen, TX, 1920-1938 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Marine Engineers, Atlantic, Great Lakes, and Gulf, 1927-1937 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Marine Engineers, Pacific, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Masters, Mates, and Pilots (Pacific), 1929-1935 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Masters, Mates, and Pilots (Atlantic and Great Lakes), 1927-1937 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Seamen, 1903-1938 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (AL, AZ, AR, and CA), 1918-1936 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (CO, CT, DE, and DC), 1921-1937 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (GA), 1920-1937 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (IL), 1920-1936 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (IN and IA), 1902-1937 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (KS and KY), 1918-1934 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (LA and ME), 1920-1934 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (MA), 1916-1936 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (MA, Boston), 1913-1936 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (MI and MN), 1915-1937 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (MO, MT, and NH), 1923-1935 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (NJ and NY), 1920-1938 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (OH and OK), 1918-1937 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (OR and PA), 1919-1936 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (RI, SC, and TN), 1919-1937 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (TX, UT, WA, and WV), 1917-1937 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees (WI and Canada), 1922-1937 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Teamsters (AL, AZ, and CA), 1919-1937 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Teamsters (CO, CT, DC, FL, and GA), 1929-1937 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Teamsters (IL, except Chicago), 1922-1937 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Teamsters, Auto Livery through Coal Drivers (IL, Chicago), 1921-1937 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Auto Livery; Baggage and Parcel Drivers; Bakery, Cracker, Pie and Yeast Wagon Drivers; Bone and Tallow; Building Materials; Cigar, Tobacco and Cigarette Salesmen and Drivers; Coffee, Cheese, Butter and Egg Drivers and Salesmen; Commission Drivers; Coal Drivers
  - Teamsters, Dairy Employees through Grease Teamsters (IL, Chicago), 1921-1939 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Dairy Employees; Excavating, Grading, Asphalt, Cinders and Private Scavenger; Florists Drivers; Furniture and Department Store Employees; General Teamsters; Grease Teamsters
  - Teamsters, Ice Cream Drivers through Newspaper Delivery Drivers (IL, Chicago), 1922-1938 (Box 18, Folder 1)